Your IP:

How do we know this? EVERY WEBSITE you use knows your IP, unless you use a VPN.

Your location:

How do we know this? EVERYONE on the Internet knows this. When your IP is visible, websites can know your location. (This has nothing to do with location sharing permissions)

Your ISP:

How do we know this? EVERYONE on the Internet knows this. When your IP is visible, websites can know your ISP.

Your IP address: visiblehidden

Your IP is not hidden by Bright VPN

**BrightVPN Privacy Policy**
============================

_Last Updated: Oct 07, 2021_

Bright Data Ltd. (“Bright”, “we,” or “us”) is the owner of the website brightvpn.com (“the Site”), the Bright software (“the Software”) and any accompanying services, features, content, and applications offered by us (collectively referred herein as “the Services”). We are concerned about your privacy and have designed this Privacy Policy in order to help you decide whether to use the Services. By accessing and using the Services, or providing information to us in other formats, you agree and accept the terms of this Privacy Policy as amended from time to time and consent to the collection and use of information in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy carefully and to periodically refer to it so that you understand it and any subsequent changes made to it.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE STOP USING THE SERVICES IMMEDIATELY AND [UNINSTALL](https://brightvpn.com/faq#how-to-i-uninstall-brightvpn) WHERE RELEVANT.

### What types of information do we collect?

We do not track nor store logs of your browsing activity, including no logging of browsing history, traffic destination, data content, or DNS queries. We do store general technical details which help us with troubleshooting and improving BrightVPN. Such storage is for short periods of time only.

We collect the following types of data from you when you use the Services:

* Personal Information: we may collect and retain your IP address, and **in case you provide it (as of 7-Oct-2021, this information is not required to use the Services)**, your name and email address, screen name, payment and billing information or other information we may ask from time to time, but only information which will be required for the on-boarding process and services provisioning. **In case you create an account**  **on the Services** **(as of 7-Oct-2021, this is not required to use the Services)** you are able to do so by using your credentials with a designated third party website or service (“Third Party Account”) such as Gmail®. Doing so will enable you to link your account and your Third Party Account. If you choose this option, a Third Party Account pop-up box will appear that you will need to approve in order to proceed, and which will describe the types of information that we will obtain. This information includes your Personal Information stored on your Third Party Account, such as user-name, email address, profile picture, birth date, gender and preferences. Any Anonymous Information that is specifically connected or linked to any Personal Information, is treated by us as Personal Information, as long as such connection or linkage exists. **For the avoidance of doubt, as of 7-Oct-2021, there is no need to provide any information or create an account to use the Services.**
* Log Data: Log data may include your outgoing VPN IP server address, connection timestamp, operating system, browser, version of VPN client installed and other technical details which help us with troubleshooting and improving BrightVPN. Such storage is for short periods of time only.

### How do we use your information?

As of 7-Oct-2021 there is no need to provide any information or create an account to use the Services.  

In case you provide us with your information, we may use it in order to provide you with the Service. This means that we will use the information to set up your account, provide you with support regarding the Service, communicate with you for updates, marketing offers or concerns you may have and conduct statistical and analytical research to improve the Service.

### Information sharing in case of extraordinary circumstances

We do not rent or sell any Personal Information. We may disclose minimal Personal Information to other trusted third party service providers or partners for the purposes of providing you with the Services, storage and analytics. We may also transfer or disclose Personal Information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, only when it’s necessary.

In extraordinary circumstances, we may also share your Personal Information and other information if and only if it’s necessary to: (1) comply with law, regulation, subpoena or court order; (2) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security, violation of our policies or technical issues; (3) enforce the provisions of this Privacy Policy or any other agreements between you and us, including investigation of potential violations thereof; (4) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of us, its partners, its affiliates, users, or the public.

### Processing of data outside the EEA

Please note that some data recipients may be located outside the EEA. In such cases we will share your data only with recipients located in such countries as approved by the European Commission as providing adequate level of data protection, or enter into legal agreements ensuring an adequate level of data protection.

### Security and Confidentiality

We use industry-standard information, security tools, and measures, as well as internal procedures and strict guidelines to prevent information misuse and data leakage. Our employees are subject to confidentiality obligations. We use measures and procedures that substantially reduce the risks of data misuse, but we cannot guarantee that our systems will be absolutely safe. If you become aware of any potential data breach or security vulnerability, you are requested to contact us immediately. We will use all measures to investigate the incident, including preventive measures, as required.

### Your Choices and Rights

**You do not need to provide any personal information to use the Services,** but in case you do, we strive to give you ways to update your information quickly or to delete it – unless we have to keep that information for legitimate business or legal purposes. When updating your personal information, we may ask you to verify your identity before we can act on your request. If you are a resident of California, United States, you have the right to send us a written request regarding a list of Personal Information categories that we may have disclosed to third parties or to which we may have given to third parties, and the details of such third parties.

If you are a resident of the European Union, please note that the following rights specifically apply regarding your personal information: (1) Receive confirmation as to whether or not personal information concerning you is being processed, and access your stored personal information, together with supplementary information; (2) Receive a copy of personal information you directly volunteer to us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format; (3) Request rectification of your personal information that is in our control; (4) Request erasure of your personal information; (5) Object to the processing of personal information by us; (6) Request to restrict processing of your personal information by us; (7) Lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

However, please note that these rights are not absolute, and may be subject to our own legitimate interests and regulatory requirements.

To exercise such right, you may contact us at: [\[email protected\]](https://brightvpn.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

### Retention

As of 7-Oct-2021 there is no need to provide any information or create an account to use the Services.

In case you provide it, we will retain your personal information for as long as necessary to provide the Service, and as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our policies. Under applicable regulations, we will keep records containing client personal data, account opening documents, communications and anything else as required by applicable laws and regulations.

We may rectify, replenish or remove incomplete or inaccurate information, at any time and at our own discretion.

### Cookies

When you use our Site, we may store cookies on your computer (as well as other tracking technologies like web beacons and pixels) in order to facilitate and customize your use of our Site. A cookie is a small data text file, which a website stores on your computer’s hard drive (if your web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you to us. Our cookies may store information regarding your account information. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but such disabling may cause some of the features of our Site to not operate properly and your online experience may be limited.

We also use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about your use of the Site. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this Site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy.

### Information Warranty Disclaimer

Notwithstanding anything else in this Policy, we are not responsible for the accuracy, correctness, and security of any of the information we gather, store, and disclose to you or to anyone else.

Our policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent you disclose your information to other parties or sites throughout the internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Accordingly, we encourage you to read the terms and conditions and privacy policy of each third party that you choose to disclose information to.

### Change of Ownership

In the event of a change of ownership or control of all or a part of Bright, including without limitation through acquisition, merger, or sale, we reserve the right to transfer all or part of the Personal Information and Anonymous Information we store in our systems. You acknowledge that in the event of bankruptcy, insolvency, or receivership, we may have no control over the use and transfer of your personal information.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

This Policy may be revised from time to time at our sole discretion, so please check it regularly. The last revision will be reflected in the “Last Updated” heading. Any change of this policy will be posted on the Site. Your continued use of the Services following any such changes will be considered as you consent to the amended Privacy Policy.

### Contact Us

If you feel that your privacy was not treated in accordance with our Privacy Policy, or if you believe that your privacy has been compromised by any person in the course of using the Services, please contact Bright  at: [\[email protected\]](https://brightvpn.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) and our privacy officer shall promptly investigate.

© 2021 Bright Data Ltd. All Rights Reserved.

General

Policies

Get in touch

* [\[email protected\]](https://brightvpn.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
* [\[email protected\]](https://brightvpn.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Supported devices

© Copyright 2023 Bright Data Ltd. | All rights reserved

#### Install BrightVPN Desktop App

To use BrightVPN, allow BrightData to occasionally access websites through your device. BrightData will:

* ONLY access public Internet web pages
* NEVER slow down your device or Internet connection
* NEVER access or collect your personal information, except IP address – see privacy policy

Approved business

Secure BrightData cloud

Your device

Public website

Agree & Install

(use available device resources)

Full terms of service

You are 2 min. away from being fully secure with FREE Premium VPN!
------------------------------------------------------------------

Cleared by major Anti-Virus engines!

We are confident that Bright VPN is 100% safe  
Still receiving an error message? [Click here ›](https://brightvpn.com/faq#why-am-i-receiving-an-error-when-downloading-brightvpn-what-can-i-do)

Downloading **Bright VPN - the best FREE VPN** in the world, [read more](https://brightvpn.com/faq)

Want to earn 100 Buffs?
-----------------------

1. **Install** the exe file on your tastbar below.
2. **That’s it!**  
    Just keep **Bright VPN installed**, and use it only when you need.

**100 Buffs** will be added to your account automatically after **30 days of activity\*.**

\*in order to qualify, your device must stay on for **least 30** days (over a course 60 days).

**Bright VPN is the best** FREE VPN in the world, [read more](https://brightvpn.com/)

#### How to install

##### BrightVPN - Desktop App

1. **Click BrightVPN-1.0.25.dmg** to open it Click [here](#) if your download doesn’t start 
2. **Drag** BrightVPN icon to “Applications” to install 
3. **Open** “BrightVPN” from “Applications” to run BrightVPN

Bright VPN is available for Windows Operating System at the moment.

Bright VPN is currently unavailable in this region. If you believe this is wrong, please send an email to [\[email protected\]](https://brightvpn.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
